now moving to slide 16 i didn't want to say a word on the pipeline readouts for the rest of the year
of the year we have quite a bit happening and we're excited about that so in the first half i
already mentioned
the rhapsody sindhu positive readout we did have unalamab readout and warm autoimmune hemolytic
anemia which did not meet statistical significance so we won't be taking that forward but we don't
expect that to be a read-through to icp where we already have positive second line data and we'll
look forward to the first line data in the second half we also have data in house now for bota plan
which confirm our approach for the phase three study based on that data we feel very comfortable
taking the 10 milligram dose now forward into the pivotal phase three readout we are in
collaboration with our partner ptc now discussing the best next steps for that medicine including
further interactions as well with with the fda and we'll keep everyone apprised as we continue
continue to progress that medicine forward we also are on track as well for the fshd biomarker
cohort readout as well our plan would be to ultimately disclose that to the public and to the
data after we've had any discussions with fda to understand better if the data meets the standard
for an accelerated approval we do not have that data in house yet but we do expect it over the
course of the remainder of the first half other important readouts include of course the paula
carson readout which i'm sure we can discuss the remy brutinib ms readout which allowed two
replicate studies the del disaran dm1 a study which i also mentioned and then we've accelerated
now the rhapsodo hs program
into the second half of this year that study enrolled extremely quickly so very excited
because that will give us another or a first oral option for patients with hs we also have our qcz
484 sirna for hypertension uh base two data uh reading out and then lastly a bhb rils trim2
antibody reading out as well in in the second half so with that i will hand it over to mccool
thank you very much boss
and good morning good afternoon everyone i will now take you through our financial results for
the first quarter which as fast mentioned were strong despite significant u.s generic entries
as always my comments refer to growth rates in constant currencies unless otherwise noted
slide 18 please our q1 results as expected were impacted by uxgx erosion